In this vast desert.
many dynasties were established
leaving behind countless legends.
Over thousands of years,
these dynasties rose and fell.
All that remains is this desert.
Beneath it lies a vast treasure
hidden deep belowthe burning sand.
No one can open the door to the treasure:
it is protected by a group of secret guards.
They have guarded this desert for generations
The legend says only the leader of the guards
can be called the "Eagle of the Desert"
Every one of the guards
is master of an oriental martial art.
Every 2 decades, a new leader is selected.
A new 'Eagle of the Desert'
When a new leader is chosen,
his opponent will be cast out.
In the desert, power is everything
Only the victor survives.
No one remembers the loser
For many years, countless explorers
have come to this desert,
hoping to find its great treasure.
Few of them returned alive.
What keeps the legend going
is the "Eagle of the Desert"
Hello?
Miss Lan, you know the deadline has long passed?
I don't care what happened to you
3 days, You're allowed only 3 more days.
This is an ultimatum.
Chief editor, can I change the topic?
I'm so fed up with these
explorations and tomb raiders
Tell you what? I've a great idea for a romance...
Who wants to read a romance?
The readers of Qidian Chinese Literature Online
are all waiting for the sequel to Ghost Town.
Send me the draft in 3 days
Otherwise you'll be fired!
Fired? He's threatening me?
Give me some more time, please
I've been writing.
What happened? Being chased by the editor?
Dad.
Hey, you haven't come home for ages.
Come have dinner with me tomorrow night.
But I...
So that's it I'll wait for you.
Excuse me, please write, "To Pork Rib"
P-O-R-K R-I-B
I was born in the year of pig.
Thank you so much!
Sir, what would you like to drink?
We came here for business, not drinking.
We heard that they never question
the provenance ofthe goods
Therefore our master
decided to send us here with these antiques
We've travelled across all of Siberia.
We hope you can offer us a good price
As long as they're genuine,
I promise it'll be worth your while.
Are you implying they're fakes?
We'll see whether they're genuine or not
when they're examined by our expert.
Just wait here.
He'll be here in a minute.
So you're the expert?
A Macedonian bronze...US$500,000
A mediaeval gold sculpture! Cool!
A Chinese bronze bell? Let me try.
This is not for you,
This is our master's alarm clock.
It's only peaceful because he's asleep.
If you strike the bell and wake him up,
we'll be in trouble
I see
You stole it, right?
No, my mom gave it to me.
"My mom gave it to me"?
No matter, I'll confiscate it
What? Confiscate it?
You mean you're stealing it from me?
Yes
FYI, I'm not stealing them from you.
I simply return them to where they belong.
Understand?
Don't strike it!
No...
Don't! Please don't.
Don't!
Run!
Crazy people!
Come on!
I never get scared, I'll just kick your ass
Tell me if it hurts, OK?
It must be quite valuable
Let me see,
what we find today is...
People later discovered that
in many ancient tombs
there was nothing but a skeleton.
Not even a single artifact
Let me tell you,
this is called a "pauper's burial"
Master Hua,
I heard a batch of antiques just arrived
Well...most of them are fake.
According to historians.
The most daring tomb raider in history...
You bought a lot!
Come on, he's giving things away again.
Master Hua, have you made up your mind?
Made up my mind? About what?
The Lost City!
I've found out who has the map
Our dream is coming true!
Pork Rib, how many times have I told you?
The chance of coming out alive
from that place is very slim!
Besides, I don't believe there is a genuine map.
Yes, there is This one is genuine!
Master Hua, you don't want to waste
your life away like this, right?
If we can find that map,
everything will be settled!
Do you remember last time? If...
You're helping yourself not me!
Pork Rib, are you afraid of dying?
No, I'm not.
Let me make it clear to you
You're not afraid of dying,
but that doesn't mean you won't die
Master Hua, you've finally agreed!
Just hang in there a little longer.
We're nearly there
This bag, take it
Everything you retrieved
has been returned to its country of origin.
Here is a new case
Qiaofei, look at this
An ancient city lost in the 11th century
Once upon a time, there was a king
He had the largest glowing pearl in the world.
The pearl was in the city
When Genghis Khan was fighting towards the East.
100 years later,
an old warrior came out of the city,
He told someone
this secret before he died
The person was called the "Eagle of the Desert"
He led a few hundred ancient warriors
to guard the city
I saw them protect the city with my own eyes
It was at that moment that
I decided to go down this path.
To return these treasures
to where they came from.
It's Lan Ting's birthday tomorrow.
I've asked her to come over Come join us
Are you sure?
She won't be happy to see me, will she?
You're the one who won't be happy, aren't you?
Looks like...
I'm not the only one who
needs to patch things up with her
Master Tu, please don't drag
me into your family business.
Hello.
Hey, can't you concentrate on the book?
How can I? It's such trash!
Then why are you reading it?
Well... I treat it as a joke.
Wait, it's not that bad, is it?
It's not just bad but really bad.
This book is full of crap!
Full of prejudice against
archaeology and exploration
Everyone is described as a greedy opportunist.
This book of yours, I bet it won't sell
You're still a nuisance.
You're always big-headed and
you never respect other people
Hey! Your dad wants you to go home for dinner
You abandoned Mom and I
for archaeology.
Why did you come back?
Why should I go back
just because you ask me to?
Please follow the suggested route.
Sit down
Keep to the left and then turn right
Chief, let's drink a toast to you!
Chief, come on, another one
I don't know what's wrong with him
He couldn't live without meat before
But now, meat scares the shit out of him.
He must be possessed
Master Hua, come eat something
You can't live on snacks
Pork Rib,
isn't it a bit too dangerous
to abduct this girl?
Well... you don't understand.
Master Tu is really difficult.
It took me so long
to find his weakness
It was his precious daughter!
So, what are you going to do with her?
No way! Are you falling for her?
Well... I've got an idea.
Anyway, when I get the map,
I'll leave her to you Am I being fair enough?
Hello?
You thought I was joking?
I said 3 more days!
I checked my email hundreds of times
and not a single word there!
I warn you, don't ever try to test my limits
Are you listening to me?
Miss Lan, I have a boss to report to...
Anyone there?
Let me ask you nicely, OK?
I don't know where I am
You've lost your memory?
Call yourself a writer? What lame excuse is this?
Why don't you say that you
don't know who you are?
Bitch! Are you calling the police?
What do you want?
You shut up, baby!
I want something from your dad,
so you're my hostage
Then you took the wrong person
The wrong person?
You're the writer, right?
I asked for your autograph
Do you remember?
He wouldn't care about me.
You're wrong I know he loves you very much.
He'll definitely come to rescue you
Chief, someone has arrived.
How many?
One, just one
Who are you? You're not who we're looking for.
I came here on behalf of Master Tu
Who do you think you are?
Since Master Tu doesn't care,
maybe we should just kill her
If it wasn't for Master Tu,
you think I'd bother to come?
Is this genuine?
I'm an expert, you can't fool me.
Wait!
If my dad wants to rescue me,
he should come himself.
Stop fussing around!
What's the difference?
It's different I won't leave until he comes.
Your dad will never come.
So what excuse does he have this time?
He already died for the sake of this map.
That's impossible
Why are you lying to me?
My dad even asked me to have dinner with him.
No...that's impossible.
You should count yourself lucky
that you didn't go home that night.
Don't look at me like that
I would never kill anyone.
I don't kill!
I'm a gentleman!
If he had handed over the map sooner.
Master Tu wouldn't have died.
See? Told you I didn't do it!
Everyone who has seen the map has to die!
But I haven't!
Take her upstairs, quick!
Let's go!
"The Sandstorm Legion"!
I thought it was just a legend! It's true!
Bonehead, Bonehead!
Hey, that legion of something has come!
Come on, let's go
Run!
I thought you didn't want to rescue me?
Come on!
Quick!
Why did you push my bottom?
I'm so scared!
Why are you hugging me so tight?
You never did!
What are you talking about? Go away!
OK, see you
Come back!
What?
Scary!
No...I can't stand it
Come on!
Master Hua!
What happened?
We're finished!
Master Hua, hurry! Lose them!
Come on!
Quick! There's dynamite in the box
Take it out, quick!
Hurry up!
Blow them up!
Qiaofei, look up ahead...
Hold it.
What for?
Yes! We made it!
What are you looking at?
What's wrong with the chief this time?
As soon as he woke up this morning,
he ordered us to destroy all the
statues of gods in the square.
He said he dreamt of being
chased by statues last night
Chased by statues all night?
Yes, in his dream
He's been acting like this since he woke up.
Little Feather, I thought you'd gone?
Chief, I just wanted to know
what lay beyond this desert.
Well... I never thought what lay outside
this desert was another desert.
But, chief, it's still worth my efforts.
Here you are.
What is this?
I don't know.
But I saw many people fighting over it.
So it must be something valuable
It looks like the season of eagles has come.
You still like lying on your
back looking at the sky
Tears don't roll down your face
when you're staring at the sky
I'll take you back tomorrow.
I don't want to go back I want to stay
I can never understand how someone could
leave his wife and child for the desert.
I can't understand it.
I want to trace my father's steps.
I think I can find the answer.
No, you won't
Haven't you caused enough trouble?
My dad's dying wish is hidden in the map, right?
Can we stop talking about it?
Surprised to see a young guy
like you could fight so well
You're a fierce rival Good to know that
But I never thought the
"Sandstorm Legion" really existed
Luckily I grew up in the desert.
This is not a big deal to me
So I see... you'll be fine if you follow me
It's a pity that the map is gone
But you don't look worried about it at all.
Is the map fake?
Who says it's fake?
I can get it back
It's tagged!
I knew it! You're as sly as me.
Good, now we're in the same boat.
We should help each other from now on
If you need any help,
I'll definitely give you a hand
See, after the map is put on the scene
these mummies, horse riders, masked robbers
and the legion of something have all appeared.
Who knows what will show up later, right?
Just give me a shout
My name is Pork Rib
Have you finished yet?
Almost. But if I need any help,
you'll have to help me as well.
Let's be fair to each other
So, that's it!
Here, this will keep you warm
for the cold night.
Give me a shout when you need help.
Bye!
Is something wrong with your friend?
Nothing serious, he's just a little crazy
So that's it Bye
Let me know if you need any help.
Are you warm enough?
Want some?
Do you remember that I watched
you practice the piano?
I crept up to the window.
Your dad caught me and I was punished.
Would you please stop talking about my dad?
Alright, I'll stop.
Here, try some That idiot gave it to us today
Drink a bit, It'll make you feel better.
He never cared about me.
How could I care about you?
I mean my dad
You enjoy reading so much, right?
You're such a nerd
A nerd?
How dare you bring that up
What?
Now I remember...
My first visit to a book shop,
I went with you
And you vanished the day after
For 10 years.
Was it because I called you a book thief?
Why did you steal that book for me?
Well, I guess I was young and I liked you.
Liked me? In what way?
As a friend.
Otherwise, what do you think?
Right, we could talk about anything as friends.
Kind of brotherly love, right?
You look really embarrassed
A toast to you, brother.
Keep drinking.
It's best if they both get drunk.
Then I'll take the tracking device over
Can you use it?
Of course not!
Otherwise I wouldn't need you.
Master Hua, as long as you're with me,
I don't need the map
To be honest, if it weren't for you
I would never be able to realize my dream
This is the one and only time.
I've pinned all my hopes on you.
Master Hua, where are they?
Where are those bloody kids?
They're gone
Damn it! They're so bloody rude!
Stop wasting your time.
They drained the tank
Where to, Master Hua?
To the "Traveller's Village"
"Traveller's Village"?
Fantastic! The explorer's paradise.
The meeting place for desert treasure hunters.
You can buy anything
if you've got the money.
Yes,
it's a paradise and hell at the same time.
If you're not strong enough,
you'll be destroyed by others
You're just trying to scare me, right?
You no good! You no good!
Do I look good?
Yes
Louder.
Hey, you were really bad.
What do you mean?
They gave us the drink and you drained their tank
What will happen to them?
You feel sorry for them?
Why don't you go with them?
You're really nasty!
I don't think so.
The map is nearby
The map?
Hey, kid Stop!
Stop!
Stop! Come here.
Get out of my way!
Chief, they're so daring.
They're chasing me!
Aren't you tired, kid?
What?
You no good! You no good!
Chief, look how arrogant he is!
So what?
Out, all of you.